Benjamin Houghton: Hello, alright. So this is going to be the video for the transfer learning learning code Demo. And I'm pretty excited also to test out cursor today. So this is literally the 1st day I've ever used cursor. So I don't know if you guys aren't aware. Cursor is pretty neat, it's basically
Benjamin Houghton: a a version of I will. I think it's a forked version of Vs code. It's sure seems like. And I don't know. I guess Vs code is open source. I'm I'm not really. I'm not really too sure about all the politics, or I guess history. Behind
Benjamin Houghton: cursor. But essentially it's it's the Vs code code base. It sure sure seems like it looks like it acts like it. It has to be like a forked version of it, but it has a large language model integrated into it. So it recognize it basically can speak.
Benjamin Houghton: You know, I think whatever language you want like, I think the default language is English, but it it understands or it it uses, you know, large language models to take in
Benjamin Houghton: English and
Benjamin Houghton: basically generate code and and vice versa, right? So it it's been specifically trained to do to do that. So we're gonna test it out today and and see how it does for a transfer learning code demo. Right?
Benjamin Houghton: and I think specifically, what we'll do is we will use.
Benjamin Houghton: I think we're gonna just gonna go ahead and use resnet and something simple like the we'll use like the Mnist fashion data set and do a classification task. Just so we can get and see how this works. All right. So let's create a, we're gonna create a file from scratch here and call it transfer.
Benjamin Houghton: Hopefully, this video isn't too long transfer learning demo
Benjamin Houghton: and this is pretty neat way to. So if I look it already, knows that I want to do like torch
Benjamin Houghton: to use torch vision. And like, we're going to use most of these imports, maybe not all of them, but almost all of them torch. Yeah, we'll definitely use models and transforms torch vision. I wonder if it knows that? You know it's reading my directory? It might have. I'm not sure
Benjamin Houghton: if it can see all the code in this directory. But this is like my home directory on my Wsl. So there's plenty of files that use these imports and stuff like that, and it knows that the name of the file is transfer learning, Demo. So I don't know it's pretty neat, so anyways, I won't. You know. That's enough about
Benjamin Houghton: the cursor, I guess, for now. So let's see the very 1st look it's already wanting to to bring in M this fashion, because I did open a file right before I made this video, just to see if it would work. And it sure enough, it it did. I just did a couple of lines of code. So we are, gonna basically, I'm gonna be doing this for the 1st time
Benjamin Houghton: from scratch on this video, though. Alright. So we're going to define the fashion mnist data set. Yeah.
Benjamin Houghton: it? Oh, where to go?
Benjamin Houghton: Let's see. Control. LK.
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah.
Benjamin Houghton: So I don't want to do that, let's see, had, like the autocomplete there a second ago.
Benjamin Houghton: There we go. Okay. Alright.
Benjamin Houghton: oh, yeah. So look at it's pretty.
Benjamin Houghton: It's pretty smart in the sense, or I wouldn't say smart, I guess. Well trained right doesn't necessarily have an artificial intelligence, right? But it it already wants to create this, compose, define, or instantiate. This transforms dot, compose class which we'll use a lot, and it's going to transform our data to a tensor and then normalize it. And I will note that this normalized class. So it wants a mean and a standard deviation.
Benjamin Houghton: So don't just overlook this. This is pretty important for these pre-trained models. They if they were trained they expect the the images to be normalized a certain way. So before I started this video, I actually went to Pytorch's documentation just to look this up.
Benjamin Houghton: and you'll see here that all the pre-trained models
Benjamin Houghton: all expect them to be all normalized the same way for RGB, 3, right? But we'll see here in a minute that
Benjamin Houghton: we're actually not using. RGB, 3 images, because there and this is just grayscale. But you'll want to, you know, pay special attention to this if you are using like, if you're doing color images right, which
Benjamin Houghton: we're not going to do today, but maybe in the future you'll certainly be doing that in this course, I'd imagine. But or if you're taking a computer vision course which most of you watching this video probably are but anyways, this side note. So anyways, let's see how this works. So it's already defined. Our data set and our data loaders for us. Nice. Okay, batch size 64. The images are kind of small. So I'm sure that's probably fine. So let's loop over this
Benjamin Houghton: loop over the data loader and print the 1st 10 images. That's fine. That's let's do that. It's gonna print the shape for us.
Benjamin Houghton: and we'll see if this image, this data looks like, oh, yeah. So we're gonna download the data. Actually,
Benjamin Houghton: yeah, it's it's downloading to.
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah. I don't really want it here. I'm gonna delete that
Benjamin Houghton: and cause I don't want it, because so you can tell it where to download. But like, I already have the this data set right? So my route, I'm gonna say, is actually going to be home
Benjamin Houghton: then data right? And so now,
Benjamin Houghton: and I think what'll happen is, it'll see that I already have it. And it won't download it right? So let's actually, we're gonna restart the kernel. Actually, I'm just gonna
Benjamin Houghton: actually, I'm gonna do this. I wanna wanna see if this works
Benjamin Houghton: and reload the window here the reload window.
Benjamin Houghton: See what happens.
Benjamin Houghton: And so we'll have to. You know, it's gonna restart the kernel and everything. I don't.
Benjamin Houghton: You don't necessarily need to reload the window to start restart the kernel. But sometimes I just do that just because
Benjamin Houghton: you know, if it's acting buggy or something like that. But anyways, let's see what happens now.
Benjamin Houghton: So it actually still download the data. I'm not entirely sure why, but
Benjamin Houghton: actually, let's look at that directory real fast.
Benjamin Houghton: Oh, okay. So you know what? I don't have this data. I have. This Jpeg version is something I did for the deep learning demo where I converted a quote unquote custom data set to a pi torch data set. And
Benjamin Houghton: yeah, I used. I used mnist as jpegs. But anyways, that's neither here nor there. You guys probably know what I'm talking about. If you paid attention in that specific deep learning
Benjamin Houghton: lecture, or looked at the code. Okay, so anyways, we have the data. Now, cool. So
Benjamin Houghton: couple more cells here, and we see that it did print the shape here. So batch size is what we expected. 64. So it is one channel grayscale, and they're 28 by 28 images, all right, easy enough. So I mean, we could plot a few of these. I think. Actually, we could even say, you know, plot
Benjamin Houghton: the 1st 10 images? Yeah, this will work. I guess it's gonna
Benjamin Houghton: let's do this. Let's do this in another cell, though.
Benjamin Houghton: See this, how this looks?
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah, just printed one. It's kind of what I thought was, gonna happen. Let's see plot the 1st 10 images in a grid. Okay, let's
Benjamin Houghton: see what happens. Now, yeah, that's not gonna work, is it? Alright? So we might have to do something.
Benjamin Houghton: define our own function or something. Let's see.
Benjamin Houghton: define a function, define a function to plot. Okay, here we go.
Benjamin Houghton: There we go. That's what we're looking. Wow! This is pretty nice, like, I mean, I wouldn't say you should become totally relying on this cursor. But if you
Benjamin Houghton: have, like a found date, like, if you have really good python and pi torch, and you know, I'll say, you know.
Benjamin Houghton: matplotlib, numpy python, pytorch, if you know all these this really? Well, then, you know, I don't think it's okay to do stuff like this. I definitely don't recommend this for beginners, because you'll never really learn to code. You'll just be relying upon this. But, anyways, let's let's see here how this looks.
Benjamin Houghton: Now, so image train load. And then we're gonna call our function here, lot images,
Benjamin Houghton: images. But we're gonna use.
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah. And look, look, it knows to use the 1st 10. Okay, cool. Alright. So let's see this nice
Benjamin Houghton: bought that figure. Let's make this a little bit bigger and
Benjamin Houghton: nice. Okay, that's that's not bad. It's not perfect, but it gives us an idea what the data set looks like, which is all we really wanted to do for now,
Benjamin Houghton: so perfect. And actually, we could even yeah, we'll just
Benjamin Houghton: we'll leave it at that for now, I think.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay, let's put this in the same cell. Clean up the code a little bit.
Benjamin Houghton: and we don't need to print them. Image sizes either. Rid of that. Alright.
Benjamin Houghton: Alright. So I know. And I'm going pretty quick here. So this isn't gonna be quite as clean as what
Benjamin Houghton: you know, I the code that I give you guys have given you in the past. Be well, for 2 reasons. Number one.
Benjamin Houghton: There's also like, really, really great examples in your textbook. Yeah, really, I kind of wanted to.
Benjamin Houghton: This is more about like.
Benjamin Houghton: like, not making perfect code. But it's about like walking. You guys, what I'm like, what my thought process is here, like what we're doing in each step, you know, kind of showing off cursor and and kind of how fast you can do something like this rather than making it perfect like this would be something I might, you know, I'd mock up real fast, and I'd come back later and like, clean it up and make these like really nice, pretty plotting functions. And you know, I would use like figure I would use.
Benjamin Houghton: you know much.
Benjamin Houghton: you know. I I would clean up all clean this all up. Anyways, let's let's keep moving on. So now we've we've got our data loaded in. We know what size it is. Now, we can define our model. So define a function to get a resnet model.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay, see if it knows what? Yeah. It did. So it knows exactly what we want.
Benjamin Houghton: yeah, we're gonna want to freeze the layers exactly what we want to do. So
Benjamin Houghton: with, you know that we talked about this a little bit in
Benjamin Houghton: during the, you know, if you watch the modern Cnn architectures. Video, we talked a little bit about transfer learning at the end, and talked about freezing layers. So what what are we doing here? So we're integrate or iterating over? All the parameters. And we're saying, if it requires grad equals false. Okay, so
Benjamin Houghton: what are we? What are we doing here? If if doesn't require the gradient, then pytorch is not going to store
Benjamin Houghton: the gradient for that tensor
Benjamin Houghton: of weights. And then it won't get updated like in a training loop. So basically we don't want to overwrite all of Resnet's
Benjamin Houghton: awesome feature ex, you know, feature, extraction.
Benjamin Houghton: knowledge, or that it's been learned from like something like image. I think you know pretty sure that the Resident I'm not 100% sure. But
Benjamin Houghton: you know, maybe we should look real fast. It should have been trained on on resnet.
Benjamin Houghton: Let's see if we can just pull that up real fast. Maybe
Benjamin Houghton: I'm sorry Resnet should have been trained. Sorry, I'm trying to
Benjamin Houghton: think, encode at the same time and talk some of the stuff I'm saying doesn't make sense. I apologize. What I'm trying to say is that this resnet model should have been trained on Imagenet. Right? Let's see, let's see, what's the search for Imagenet.
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah. Imagenet.
Benjamin Houghton: yeah, I don't know.
Benjamin Houghton: Oh, another thing we're gonna have to deal with is that these these?
Benjamin Houghton: I just realized right? So, imagenet these were, if you remember our 2 24 by 2 24. Right? So let's
Benjamin Houghton: you know, I want to print.
Benjamin Houghton: This is fine for now. It knows to put 10 classes in here.
Benjamin Houghton: Let's take a look at our model here and like, I wanna got resnet. Okay.
Benjamin Houghton: find a function to train the model. Sure? Why not? But anyways, right now, I just wanna
Benjamin Houghton: I want to print the model just to see what is in it. Okay? Alright,
Benjamin Houghton: using a parameter. Pre-trained is the appreciate. Okay? Yeah. Depracted. We want to use use weights in in the okay, sure.
Benjamin Houghton: See if that fixes weights. Default. Interesting.
Benjamin Houghton: interesting! Alright. So I didn't realize that you could.
Benjamin Houghton: Which makes sense. You can kind of specify.
Benjamin Houghton: Alright. So we'll sure we'll use the the resnet.
Benjamin Houghton: Well, let's see what arguments this even takes real fast
Benjamin Houghton: optional. It's optional.
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah. Works vision.
Benjamin Houghton: Hmm, let's go back to the documentation. See if we can
Benjamin Houghton: see this is like, wonder what version of
Benjamin Houghton: works vision, beachfront, which vision models is what we need.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay?
Benjamin Houghton: And then we'll wait.
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah, interesting. Okay
Benjamin Houghton: for every provided architecture.
Benjamin Houghton: Oh, maybe we should look at this, because maybe we want a specific architecture. Oh, wait. No, obviously, for every architecture that means like pretty sure. That means like resnet, 18 or 50 or 1. 0, whatever like how many layers there are.
Benjamin Houghton: all right, we're just going to use the default weights.
Benjamin Houghton: I am going to Google default
Benjamin Houghton: resnet 18 weights. Cause like, I wanna make sure
Benjamin Houghton: want to see which data set.
Benjamin Houghton: yeah, I can also use. I think I can use cursor just to ask like.
Benjamin Houghton: ask a question. Right? Let's see what happens. How do I do that here chat?
Benjamin Houghton: Where is the chat?
Benjamin Houghton: See, I'm really new, like, I said. I don't even know how to open chat. And and you guys probably know how to do this. And I I might not even know how to do it. Okay, open chat in cursor Google, that real fast.
Benjamin Houghton: Sorry I didn't want this video to be so long, guys, hopefully, I'll try and speed it up here.
Benjamin Houghton: You guys can always watch it in fast mode. Right? All right. So how do we open chat?
Benjamin Houghton: Control? L, okay, that worked well.
Benjamin Houghton: alright. Well, let's just do this alright. So
Benjamin Houghton: What waits are provided with resnet and pytorch.
Benjamin Houghton: Specifically what data set was used.
Benjamin Houghton: The train, the model model slash weights.
Benjamin Houghton: All right, Pytorch related. Resnet.
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah. Imagenet. Right? That's what I thought, but
Benjamin Houghton: just wanted to make sure, because obviously it doesn't. I mean, obviously, it doesn't make sense to train on something like, why wouldn't it make sense to train on something like mnist. Right? Like M. This is a toy data set like, we're not getting any feature extraction power from that. We need something with a massive amount of classes, so that resnet learns. Like all these complex shapes and
Benjamin Houghton: hierarchies, right like it can, it finds a wheel in a car, and then, you know, it learns to the shape of a car, and so on and so forth. So it learns to extract all these different types of shapes and combinations of shapes. Right? So something like mnist is like, so it's too basic and too simple. Right? All right? So
Benjamin Houghton: cool. So let's see test
Benjamin Houghton: the model with single image. Alright.
Benjamin Houghton: Let's see what happens.
Benjamin Houghton: I think we're gonna get an error because it's not the right shape. Yeah, exactly so.
Benjamin Houghton: Expected
Benjamin Houghton: 64. Okay, yeah. So you see how it's 7 by. So this is. And if you guys can go back, you can look at the notes, actually, if you want to. But we talked about all the different resnets.
Benjamin Houghton: configurations, and we see, like the very 1st layer is 64, the very 1st layer. You know, it expects here to have
Benjamin Houghton: 3 input channels. Right? So 64 is going to be number output channels, 3 input, channels. And then 7 by 7, and I can already tell you that
Benjamin Houghton: these images are way too small. So not only do we have the incorrect number of channels, but we also have the incorrect number or incorrect image size. So I I don't know if
Benjamin Houghton: you know what I might do is just, and I wanna get rid of this layer. But this might not work like
Benjamin Houghton: resnet. Let's see color
Benjamin Houghton: image it, color image data set pie torch. I want to see if there's another easy data set we can use.
Benjamin Houghton: Well, we're really changing things on the fly now. Huh? Changing our data set. I guess I should have thought about that, should I should have
Benjamin Houghton: Cfar. So Cfar is.
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah, let's do see, let's do see far, because
Benjamin Houghton: Oh, wait. They're also colorized versions of mnist. I didn't know that. Let's see
Benjamin Houghton: colorized here. I know you guys can't even see what I'm I'm on looking on the other screen. Colorized versions of Ms. By Dorch.
Benjamin Houghton: Wonder if we can download it? I don't want to download it, though. I just
Benjamin Houghton: all right, we're just gonna use Cfar. Actually, you know we'll do something fun. We'll use Cfar 100 that might better show
Benjamin Houghton: how to do all right. This might be a better example anyways. Alright, so we're going to redefine define
Benjamin Houghton: Cfar, 10 data. No. Cfr 100, though.
Benjamin Houghton: 100.
Benjamin Houghton: There we go. Okay, cool.
Benjamin Houghton: yeah. See, this isn't the right range. There you go. But use correct
Benjamin Houghton: normalization. Vector, now, okay, it didn't know it doesn't know I'm talking about all right. So we're just gonna see, this is why you need to know what you're doing right like, because otherwise this is an this is a gotcha moment. Right? You need to be kind of. You can't just let this run wild. You have to know. You have to kind of look at every line of code and make sure you know what it's doing and and what you need to do. So let's get our our
Benjamin Houghton: normal, right? So again, torch vision models, normalization. Right? You can just type that into Google, and it'll
Benjamin Houghton: you'll be able to find what you need
Benjamin Houghton: there. So there we go. So there's the vector, we need. Okay, there's our mean and standard deviation.
Benjamin Houghton: Right?
Benjamin Houghton: okay, just copy and paste that right in
Benjamin Houghton: alright. Make this a little bit prettier.
Benjamin Houghton: So be like this.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay, that'll work.
Benjamin Houghton: alright.
Benjamin Houghton: We don't want to plot them, though.
Benjamin Houghton: I just want the shape.
Benjamin Houghton: Download them
Benjamin Houghton: alright cool. So now we have the right. So now we have the right number of channels at least. We are going to resize them, though we'll do that here in a second.
Benjamin Houghton: Alright, but in the meantime, let's let's plot them. Think we're gonna have to roll. We're not gonna be able to.
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah, it's not gonna work, cause the the channel is in the wrong spot for for numpy
Benjamin Houghton: So let's fix that real fast.
Benjamin Houghton: Blah. I am show. So you need to.
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah, look, it already knows the permutia. That's that's the word I was looking for. Change the permuti axis. So what this does is saying put make axis 0. Now, it's you're just basically redefining the order of the axes, and then before it was channel by height, by width. Now it's going to be first.st Axis is is going to be height width and then channels right? So we don't want grayscale anymore.
Benjamin Houghton: Alright, we can just get rid of this entire line of code. Actually, right? So delete this.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay, cool? Maybe we should plot the the label
Benjamin Houghton: images, labels. Yeah, let's see, and then
Benjamin Houghton: add label, let's see if we can add the label as a add label to subpot.
Benjamin Houghton: add label to image.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay, let's see if that works.
Benjamin Houghton: labels.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay, that that worked cool tensor.
Benjamin Houghton: Oh, okay, right? It's like the
Benjamin Houghton: but it's not the name. How how do? I don't know how we get the name for you to kind of off the Google, how to get
Benjamin Houghton: name of
Benjamin Houghton: works, data set porch, dataset classes.
Benjamin Houghton: Alright. So how do we get the class names?
Benjamin Houghton: It's in the Meta. Okay, well, that's fun.
Benjamin Houghton: Alright. Let's see if we can just make another get.
Benjamin Houghton: See far. 100 classes, class names.
Benjamin Houghton: Let's see right now, let's print this out. See what it looks like.
Benjamin Houghton: oh, okay, I guess they're in order. Alright.
Benjamin Houghton: Wonder happens if I just say, Yeah, let us do that.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay, cool. Alright. This is annoying, though, it's clipping the data. So what does this mean?
Benjamin Houghton: well, yeah, the data has for floats. The data has to be between. It has to be basically between 0 and one and
Benjamin Houghton: or between 0 and 2 55.
Benjamin Houghton: So what's
Benjamin Houghton: And I wonder? Like there should be like a torch like a
Benjamin Houghton: should be like a function to kind of inspect the data. So tensor inspect
Benjamin Houghton: function. Let's let's Google that right real fast.
Benjamin Houghton: you know, what's what's let's use our large language model how to inspect porch tensor.
Benjamin Houghton: whatever we already kind of knew all that. I wonder?
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah, I was hoping to see if there's like a nice function that does it all for you.
Benjamin Houghton: Right? This is what I was looking for. But I I didn't wanna like.
Benjamin Houghton: I mean, sure the statistical properties is what I'm after. Specifically,
Benjamin Houghton: So let's do this.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay, inspect a single image image dot shape label, dot really need the label shape.
Benjamin Houghton: Let's do what I want. Is this right?
Benjamin Houghton: Alright, let's just take a look at this. So what I was really was after here was the min, the Max
Benjamin Houghton: mean and standard. So I wonder if
Benjamin Houghton: it's because we're normalizing them? I'm guessing is why.
Benjamin Houghton: yeah, I wonder what happened would happen if we didn't if we didn't do this right, if we did a mean.
Benjamin Houghton: or if we didn't normalize them at all. Wonder what happened? Let's just see what happens just for curiosity.
Benjamin Houghton: We're just gonna get rid of this real fast.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay?
Benjamin Houghton: So yeah. Now that it's in the ballot range, right? The men and Max is 0 on one.
Benjamin Houghton: which is kind of what I expected, which is fine like
Benjamin Houghton: alright so cool like. Look at that, though. Crocodile, ray.
Benjamin Houghton: otter, baby bus, you know this data sets like, does the duty Imagenet contain the Cfr images?
Benjamin Houghton: No
Benjamin Houghton: good.
Benjamin Houghton: Alright. So I'm wondering if I could.
Benjamin Houghton: And I pro, I told you guys I was gonna be kind of
Benjamin Houghton: trying to be. I was gonna be kind of like quick about this, and maybe kind of sloppy. But
Benjamin Houghton: I'm starting to be like.
Benjamin Houghton: I want to. Get rid of these where that was, printouts were saying it was clipping the data, the valid range. So I'm just trying to figure out real quick how to do that.
Benjamin Houghton: Alright. So here's a quick function we found to just do it real fast. I wonder if
Benjamin Houghton: this is gonna work.
Benjamin Houghton: So now we have our normalized data.
Benjamin Houghton: And I'm gonna here's our function to unnormalize it. Real fast
Benjamin Houghton: image on normalized image. Yeah, it didn't work, did it
Benjamin Houghton: at the right?
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah, it's the right values. Here.
Benjamin Houghton: I'm gonna pause this video real quick.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay, alright. So I fix that. I pause it, because anytime I get like
Benjamin Houghton: I have to stop and, you know, spend some time debugging something that isn't super pertinent to what we're doing. I'm gonna probably try and stop the video. So you don't sit there and you know, figure out how long to fast forward.
Benjamin Houghton: But anyways, this on normalized function does work. My problem was is that I was passing an entire tensor through or entire batch of images, not a single image. So once I got a single image passing this on normalized function works. Now, right? So all we do is we? Actually, the large language model actually was nice enough to tell me
Benjamin Houghton: that we just multiply by the norm. If we take the normalized image multiplied by the standard deviation that we use, which is up here and the mean, add the mean. And we can get the on normalized version of the image. Right? So, like, we're just yeah, we're just reversing this normalization operation. So now we got rid of that pesky warning where it's telling us it's normalizing the images. So
Benjamin Houghton: in our plot function we get the on normalized version, and then we permute the axes, and we can. We can plot them. And we also add the class names to the the images cool. Alright. So now we're back to defining our model. Right? So well, actually, before we get to that, we need to resize the images. Right? So that's so. That's 1 thing we need to do here. So we not only need to. We also need to do
Benjamin Houghton: find C far
Benjamin Houghton: resized images. Oh, wait, I wait. I didn't even see that I typed this. Wow, this thing is pretty amazing. Yeah. So now we have the right size images.
Benjamin Houghton: Alright. So 2, 2, 4 cool, all right.
Benjamin Houghton: Nice.
Benjamin Houghton: Alright. Yeah. Look, they're the right size. Now we can see.
Benjamin Houghton: a let's see 5 in a 5 by 2 grade. We'll we'll know what to do. What I mean by that.
Benjamin Houghton: you know. All right, we're not. Gonna
Benjamin Houghton: we're not gonna worry about that. Okay.
Benjamin Houghton: I'm not like, I said, I'm not gonna make not gonna make everything super pretty right?
Benjamin Houghton: not gonna worry about it. Okay. So moving on resnet
Benjamin Houghton: right? So weights, weights. Yes, default weights cool.
Benjamin Houghton: All right.
Benjamin Houghton: Alright. So what are we doing here? Back to? We were talking about this before we got sidetracked by our image, sizes our dimensions, which we have the incorrect number of channels.
Benjamin Houghton: We also have the wrong image size. So both those things are fixed. Now, like we, we had to change data sets because we didn't want to find an M this data set that had color channels. So we're just going to use the Cfr data set great, and we also resize our images directly using our data set class perfect. So now we got the right size images. And let's talk about what we're doing here with resnet. We're freezing all the layers, meaning we're not going to update them during training
Benjamin Houghton: except for the fully connected layer. And yes, we need. That's correct. We need a hundred
Benjamin Houghton: classes, right? So we iterate over all the parameters in resnet. Freeze them, and then we also. But then we define a fully connected layer here that does 100
Benjamin Houghton: that's going to output 100
Benjamin Houghton: yes, instead of instead of a, you have the set of a thousand classes, there's a hundred. So the fully connected layer needs to have a hundred output nodes. Those become the logics for our
Benjamin Houghton: our activate, our final activation, which will be what should have would. Well, actually.
Benjamin Houghton: during yeah, you would use
Benjamin Houghton: softmax for because we're doing multi class classification here.
Benjamin Houghton: right? And we actually don't need to define
Benjamin Houghton: the softmax because it's actually built into the multi-class classification law loss function, anyways, that's neither here nor there. We actually talked about that in deep learning, if you don't remember but anyways, let's take a look here now. So define a function to train the model.
Benjamin Houghton: Great? Let's put this in a new cell, though, because actually.
Benjamin Houghton: don't think what we're gonna wanna do here,
Benjamin Houghton: take a look at the model.
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah. So I'm gonna I'm gonna comment this out, because it's
Benjamin Houghton: a really, I guess we'll just leave it here.
Benjamin Houghton: But yeah, we can look at this real fast. So scrollable element. You can look at all the layers. You know, I'm not
Benjamin Houghton: to keen. We might need to look at this later if we need to debug something. But for the most part it's just like a basic resident model, you know, not to say, residents basic. But we've talked about in some pretty good detail the actual architecture resident now, alright. So we have a function here to train
Benjamin Houghton: the model. But what I really want is function to to plot
Benjamin Houghton: training, progress. There are accuracy. Yeah, that's better way of saying it. Maybe alright. So
Benjamin Houghton: train loss, train accuracy, val loss, val accuracy. Okay? All right.
Benjamin Houghton: Alright.
Benjamin Houghton: Let's see here.
Benjamin Houghton: So now we're gonna add
Benjamin Houghton: epic and range number of epics.
Benjamin Houghton: I'll tell you what I am gonna do. I'm gonna cheat a little bit because I don't even I don't want to spend like 10 min trying to get like, do this from scratch or getting the Llm. To do it for me. I'm gonna take a function that you guys have. If you've taken any course with me before
Benjamin Houghton: reinforcement learning or deep learning. You've probably seen me use this function before. So where is it? It's going to be?
Benjamin Houghton: And
Benjamin Houghton: here, somewhere, deep learning pie torch models.
Benjamin Houghton: Let's open this up. I got some pretty nice plotting functions in here.
Benjamin Houghton: I I wonder if I could have just this is what I'm looking for right here.
Benjamin Houghton: yeah.
Benjamin Houghton: I don't. I don't know the the large language model one might have worked. I don't know. I didn't have enough. It's I'm doing this really quick, like.
Benjamin Houghton: not like reading through. I didn't read through every line to make sure. But anyways, let's just leave this for now. I know this function works, and we'll try to integrate that into here, define a function to train the model and plot the train
Benjamin Houghton: a training. I'll say this.
Benjamin Houghton: Let's just get rid of this.
Benjamin Houghton: I'm to train and plot train, yeah, and plot models.
Benjamin Houghton: Pull up the model plot. What model training or model, or, let's say, training progress. How about that?
Benjamin Houghton: Alright. So train and plot train loader test loader criteria, optimizer number of epics.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay, this all looks good.
Benjamin Houghton: We haven't defined an optimizer yet, or a loss function, for that matter. So we need to do that.
Benjamin Houghton: Alright.
Benjamin Houghton: alright. So here we're we're.
Benjamin Houghton: you know, place model in training mode. Okay? And then here, we're looping over
Benjamin Houghton: over the training data. And I'm just kind of like putting the comments in for our own, you know, for for our own benefit. Here.
Benjamin Houghton: All right, we're off 0. The gradient. Yeah.
Benjamin Houghton: Outputs. Okay, get the outputs from the model, calculate the loss. Or we let's do that. Let's define the loss. We haven't done that yet. Right? So let's define
Benjamin Houghton: the loss here. Due to new. So so loss is going to be equal to. Yes, that's correct. Category. Cross entropy.
Benjamin Houghton: cross entropy, loss optimizer.
Benjamin Houghton: Now let's use a better optimizer. Let's see what's a good a good optimizer or Cnn's.
Benjamin Houghton: Probably I was gonna say something like Adam or, Yeah, that's what I was thinking. If that's exactly what it went to Adam at that. Yeah, we'll use Adam
Benjamin Houghton: with weight decay.
Benjamin Houghton: Right? So
Benjamin Houghton: alright, we'll use that. Alright. So we got a loss function optimizer now, alright. And then
Benjamin Houghton: it didn't write like the entire function for us for this time, we actually kind of have to. I this is a I thought it was. Gonna I was wondering how how much we were gonna have to actually do ourselves, and how much the large language model was, gonna do alright. So
Benjamin Houghton: let's change this to like 10. It's kind of a lot
Benjamin Houghton: criterion.
Benjamin Houghton: All right. Law, stop back. Okay? So it's calculating loss here, updating the weights when the optimizer. And then we put the model in valuation mode with torch.no grad, and then we'll over the test loop over the test loader and get the outputs.
Benjamin Houghton: We get the predicted value using torch that, Max. This this gives us the logics is what this does.
Benjamin Houghton: I don't know why it's calculating the loss here. That's
Benjamin Houghton: do. We need this line? I don't know why. Well.
Benjamin Houghton: I guess if we wanted to, if we yeah.
Benjamin Houghton: I guess we wanted to plot the testing loss. I really care more about the accuracy, but we'll keep it.
Benjamin Houghton: and then the total here
Benjamin Houghton: labels dot size 0. Correct. Okay? So that's the total number of images.
Benjamin Houghton: And this is the ones that got correct. Right? So I think we needed to say here.
Benjamin Houghton: I need to say, total equals 0 and correct equals. 0, right? So every time.
Benjamin Houghton: okay, test loss.
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah, that's correct. Looks like it's correct. At least add the loss, test loss, the test accuracy
Benjamin Houghton: and then plot the training. But we need to get the train loss in the train. Accuracy.
Benjamin Houghton: Yep, that's correct, except
Benjamin Houghton: don't need to. We don't need to do it.
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah, we don't wanna add the accuracy. Yeah, see, this is kind of
Benjamin Houghton: I see how it's easy to make mistakes using cursor because
Benjamin Houghton: you really gotta kind of you really gotta kind of pay attention to what you're doing here. All right. So what we're doing here, we're looping over all the images in the train loader. Right? So in a single epic, we're gonna loop over basically the entire data set here all right and basically
Benjamin Houghton: for images late. This is a single batch. Right? So for this, for so this represents the entire data. Set this one round of it. Yeah, let's go ahead and print that. Sure. Why not cool? Actually, I don't want to print anything, because we're going to have the plots.
Benjamin Houghton: So we're gonna have the epic. Here
Benjamin Houghton: it's going. We're gonna this is gonna for one iteration. Here is one is entire. Is the entire data set right?
Benjamin Houghton: and one iteration. Here is one batch. So for every single batch.
Benjamin Houghton: we're gonna calculate the number total that how many are in the batch, which is just the batch size. How many are correct in the batch, and then we're gonna add, and then at the end.
Benjamin Houghton: at the very, very end of the bat, after we've gone. And every time we're gonna we're gonna add that in at the very, very end we've gone. Now we've looped over the entire data set. We're gonna add the accuracy. So it's just gonna get the accuracy for
Benjamin Houghton: the, it's just gonna get one accuracy number for the entire epic, which is fine, which is. And then that's the same thing we're doing here. We're gonna after we've looped over all the test images. We'll get the entire. We'll get the accuracy and the loss right?
Benjamin Houghton: see, the loss is kind of funny because well, the the loss is kind of funny, because
Benjamin Houghton: I don't like that. Because the law. See? This is, I'm not sure how to handle this, because
Benjamin Houghton: we also need to get the batch like it's gonna be the
Benjamin Houghton: the loss is calculated on a per batch, right? Not a per epic. Right? So with the testing data.
Benjamin Houghton: yeah, it's not even. We're not even keeping track of it here, though. Train loss. Yeah, it's getting.
Benjamin Houghton: This would just this is getting every batches loss. But this is but down here it's just getting it, for the last batch is what would happen.
Benjamin Houghton: So the question is is, do we want to plot
Benjamin Houghton: the loss? For like we can just we could just plot
Benjamin Houghton: trying to look at my function here. Train loss.
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah. So we're just plotting the last one. I mean, we could do like the average loss. Let's do the average train loss. How about that?
Benjamin Houghton: Instead of saying, Yeah, so instead of doing this right, we're gonna say.
Benjamin Houghton: also this, I just realized we have another bug here, total equals 0 correct equals 0 say, average loss. There we go
Benjamin Houghton: equals 0. And then
Benjamin Houghton: we're gonna say, we're gonna get rid of this line. And we're gonna say, average loss.
Benjamin Houghton: It's equal to
Benjamin Houghton: what is the average loss is going to be equal to.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay, I think that's correct. Actually.
Benjamin Houghton: And then. Now we're gonna say, train, there we go.
Benjamin Houghton: And we should need to do the same thing down here. Really. So
Benjamin Houghton: yeah, there, it knew what I wanted to do. Okay, I think that's I think that's pretty good.
Benjamin Houghton: We'll say, average, we'll say,
Benjamin Houghton: average loss. Here
Benjamin Houghton: we're not even plotting the
Benjamin Houghton: Oh, here we are
Benjamin Houghton: okay.
Benjamin Houghton: Alright, let's just run this and see what kind of crazy errors we get train and plot. All right. Cool epics. Let's just do like 5, because I don't really know what to expect exactly.
Benjamin Houghton: I wonder how many I didn't. You know I didn't even look to see the total number of
Benjamin Houghton: images are in this data set.
Benjamin Houghton: Looks like it's taking a while. You know what we also need to do, too.
Benjamin Houghton: let's stop this and cause you know what we're gonna do is we're gonna do this all on the Gpu. Actually. So we're gonna modify all the code to do that should only take a second
Benjamin Houghton: to do that check. If G, it's like, it's listening to me like.
Benjamin Houghton: okay, we're using cuda all right.
Benjamin Houghton: I wonder if we can do where we want to do, I can't remember where where or when
Benjamin Houghton: to send data to Gpu. I wonder at what I can't remember where we want to do it
Benjamin Houghton: in the I guess we do it. Yeah, in the looks like it wants us to do it in the training loop. Okay.
Benjamin Houghton: don't move the entire data set. Don't forget to move the labels. Yada, Yada, Yada, Yada, send it back to the CPU. Okay, cool.
Benjamin Houghton: So basically, it's saying
Benjamin Houghton: right to do it here in our training loop. Okay, well, let's do that. Then. Look images to device. Yep, to device alright. And then
Benjamin Houghton: once it gets back we have to move them back off of the device right?
Benjamin Houghton: which I think it's fine.
Benjamin Houghton: When do we want to do that? We want to do it here because we're using this to plot. Right? So
Benjamin Houghton: correct, Dot, let's see, when do we want to send it back
Benjamin Houghton: from the model to the device.
Benjamin Houghton: Let's take a look here, our torch models and see.
Benjamin Houghton: Think this is all on the CPU.
Benjamin Houghton: Am I even using the?
Benjamin Houghton: I guess I don't. I guess I don't use the Gpu in this file alright, so that can't help us. But I know that we're gonna have to send it
Benjamin Houghton: back to pretty sure
Benjamin Houghton: what? Let's see, I don't know what's gonna I'm pretty sure we had to send it back to the CPU before we can plot it, but we'll find out real fast.
Benjamin Houghton: all right. So oh, I also wanted to see how many images there were. Let's see.
Benjamin Houghton: loop over data set count total images.
Benjamin Houghton: Oh, yeah, that's right. It has this built in length.
Benjamin Houghton: We don't need to loop over at 50,000. So what is that?
Benjamin Houghton: 50,000 over.
Benjamin Houghton: How many batches is that
Benjamin Houghton: number of images and data set, and then number. See
Benjamin Houghton: number of batches? There we go.
Benjamin Houghton: 700. That's not too bad. I think we'll be fine.
Benjamin Houghton: alright, we're gonna restart kernel, and I'll probably run all this. But wanna make sure that
Benjamin Houghton: I get this correct like. I don't think that I can just plot.
Benjamin Houghton: Let's see.
Benjamin Houghton: Send lost and accurate. Send the loss and accuracy to the CPU.
Benjamin Houghton: Doesn't know what I'm talking about
Benjamin Houghton: how to send results of training back.
Benjamin Houghton: I'll just go. I'll just you do this rather than looking at some of my old code.
Benjamin Houghton: Wow! That was fast. Okay, use CPU for tensors.
Benjamin Houghton: considering. Consider using detach. If you don't need gradients.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay.
Benjamin Houghton: CPU tensor.
Benjamin Houghton: So I think for single values, it might not matter actually.
Benjamin Houghton: For scalar tensors for counting.
Benjamin Houghton: Alright! Let's find out.
Benjamin Houghton: While this is running. We'll we'll take a closer look at what the Llm. Is saying so.
Benjamin Houghton: Oh, boy, this is an interesting game.
Benjamin Houghton: Whoa, what's the problem here?
Benjamin Houghton: Model? So we got a pro somewhere in
Benjamin Houghton: input type, torch, dot, float tensor and weight type.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay.
Benjamin Houghton: I'm not really sure. I know what this means.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay, yeah, I thought, maybe that's the case. But
Benjamin Houghton: it told me to move the label. I I thought I did move it to the
Benjamin Houghton: moving both images and labels to, you know, I saw that I thought maybe it was Gpu CPU error, but
Benjamin Houghton: didn't. Don't know where that's occurring.
Benjamin Houghton: Oh, wait.
Benjamin Houghton: What? Line? 42. 0, okay.
Benjamin Houghton: yeah. So obviously, we didn't do it here. Images. Yeah, there we go cool. So it got through the entire training batch. Awesome. Alright!
Benjamin Houghton: Let's resume.
Benjamin Houghton: Oh, you know what
Benjamin Houghton: Since we got that error, I think it would have already done it actually did an entire epic on training the model.
Benjamin Houghton: So
Benjamin Houghton: it would already. It's already gonna have like an entire epics worth. We're not gonna see any training progress.
Benjamin Houghton: because it's probably only going to take like one epic to train this model. So it would already been it would be, it would be on the second app epoch, basically. But it would only plot the 1st one, I
Benjamin Houghton: think. Yeah. So let's let's restart the kernel and run it again, cause that only that didn't take very long, anyway. Is it to plot to to get through an entire E box? So alright. And while that's doing, I'm gonna look at this again. I don't actually think we need to worry about converting it
Benjamin Houghton: for single values. You can just use this loss. Dot. Item, i i i guess that
Benjamin Houghton: moves things back to the CPU. If it's just a single value.
Benjamin Houghton: detach. I want to read this. So grab that CPU lost that. Oh, yeah, look, it worked. Okay. Cool
Benjamin Houghton: test accuracy training. Alright, looks like everything's working.
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah. I actually didn't know that, or if I did, I forgot which you know it's a lot to know pi torch so you can easily forget stuff. So don't hold me, you know.
Benjamin Houghton: don't hold it against me. I think that might conclude our video. I think what I'll do well, not completely conclude it, but I think what I'll do is I'll I'll pause the video. I'm gonna let it train
Benjamin Houghton: And then I'm going to resume. And we'll talk about the results.
Benjamin Houghton: All right. So we're back here at the results of the 1st 5 epochs.
Benjamin Houghton: I could see that the test accuracy is already starting to level off, and the loss is actually starting to go up. We'll see what happens. But
Benjamin Houghton: that's not too bad. I'm going to say, you know.
Benjamin Houghton: 55%, 60%, I mean, with resnet resnet's not the most advanced architecture.
Benjamin Houghton: that's pretty good, considering there's a hundred classes, you know. So I don't really know what type of ex
Benjamin Houghton: what? Let's see, what accuracy should we expect with resnet on Cfar 100.
Benjamin Houghton: Let's see if it knows.
Benjamin Houghton: Yeah. So basically, it's saying
Benjamin Houghton: with fine tuning on freezing some layers.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay? So with some, yeah, like with optimizations.
Benjamin Houghton: you're you're using a fully frozen. Yeah, we already it is fully frozen
Benjamin Houghton: basic augmentation. We're not basically doing any augmentation. So that's a good point.
Benjamin Houghton: the training for only 5 epochs. Yeah. So we could improve it. That's not really the purpose of today's video.
Benjamin Houghton: This would probably take us another 30 40 min to implement even using cursor. So you know, that's really. I just wanted to show you like how fast you can get it. But it's pretty impressive. There's a hundred classes that like in a matter. I don't know how long this video is. I can't, doesn't tell me. I wish Zoom told me how long my recording currently was. But it's it's getting up there now, maybe over about an hour or longer, but
Benjamin Houghton: we're able to get you gotta remember there's a hundred classes. If we were doing something like mnist like this would have been like a hundred.
Benjamin Houghton: you know, something like simpler, I think that it got even really close to like 100% not a hundred percent accuracy, but probably in the nineties with like, with something like the M this fashion. You, of course, like, that's such a simple data set you don't necessarily need to use resnet. But you can see that using we just plugged in resident. It did pretty good right off the bat. I think we're gonna stop here because.
Benjamin Houghton: you know, it's saying, with the basic frozen background, you can expect 45 to 55 test accuracy. Which is about where we are. We're a little bit above that. So I'm not gonna sure I'm not sure, really, is even worth to go in deeper, you know. Maybe maybe we'll just hit this one more time and let do another. Let do another 5 e box. But
Benjamin Houghton: it's gonna redefine our train loss and test loss and everything. I just realized that I should have probably
Benjamin Houghton: wrote this function to return those things or save them or something, so that you can just keep resuming. Not a big deal. Let's just see.
Benjamin Houghton: We'll see what happens now.
Benjamin Houghton: where we're at. I mean, you can. It actually looks like
Benjamin Houghton: maybe it is getting a little bit better.
Benjamin Houghton: I'll tell you what I'll do. I'm gonna pause. I'll stop this, actually. And I'm gonna change this to 10. I'll pause the recording, and then we'll come back and we'll we'll talk about it or restart the kernel
Benjamin Houghton: and redo this
Benjamin Houghton: and we'll run all.
Benjamin Houghton: And then when this is done, I'll that'll probably be the end of the video. We'll talk about it real fast, and that'll probably be the end. So let me pause this, and we'll see here in a minute.
Benjamin Houghton: Alright! So I changed my mind. I am going to implement some of these changes. Some just some like really basic
Benjamin Houghton: transform, like some very, very basic
Benjamin Houghton: augmentations here. Right? So we are, gonna do
Benjamin Houghton: let's see horizontal flip, random rotation, random cropping and then after that
Benjamin Houghton: we are going to resize it
Benjamin Houghton: and then create a tensor from it?
Benjamin Houghton: And then we'll finally normalize it. Okay, so this is, gonna take a little bit longer.
Benjamin Houghton: This. So this is some better data augmentation. It's still pretty basic. But this is gonna get us, I think, a little bit better. And then we are gonna add in, I've never you. I've used. Now I've used learning rate schedulers before.
Benjamin Houghton: but I have never
Benjamin Houghton: used one like this. So this is actually new to me. It's pretty cool. I've done this manually before, but reduce learning rate on plateau. That's pretty nifty. I've done like a lot of times in the past. I've trained models, trained models, and then, like, I'll see where they start plateauing, and then I'll kind of like back calculate when to reduce it from that. This is pretty nifty
Benjamin Houghton: So we're going to try this out this learning rate scheduler.
Benjamin Houghton: And let's see,
Benjamin Houghton: yeah, we're gonna implement all these. We're gonna implement these changes and see what kind of results we get now? I gotta figure out where
Benjamin Houghton: where to put where do we? Where we put the scheduler in here.
Benjamin Houghton: how we plug in or plug it into the rest of our code when to call.
Benjamin Houghton: Think it's scheduler dot step, or something like that. If my memory serves me correct when
Benjamin Houghton: what's went? I did not mean to type that
Benjamin Houghton: learning rate. Scheduler should be stepped based on the little area.
Benjamin Houghton: So here's an example. Scheduler dot step validation loss. All right, schedule that step
Benjamin Houghton: for all. Okay? So yeah, that makes sense. So that's pretty
Benjamin Houghton: alright. So it's gonna take
Benjamin Houghton: sorry. Let me just put this in here, and then I'll say what I was. Gonna say, yeah, so like a normal scheduler, you would just like if it was like just a linear or an exponential, or whatever type of step it is. You know, we've even defined our own schedulers before. Right? Like a warmup scheduler
Benjamin Houghton: the cosine warmup scheduler that we use for large language models and deep learning. The deep learning class. This one
Benjamin Houghton: actually takes an argument just, you know, like the other ones are just. They have a certain schedule. Well, this is only gonna step, if you know, based upon if we get a stall with the average loss. Specifically the
Benjamin Houghton: Oh, I just realized something.
Benjamin Houghton: This should be. We had a we had a little bug here, so it was only recording the last, the last batch, which is fine, I mean before. But
Benjamin Houghton: yeah, that's a bug, anyways. Now, it should be. Get the entire loss of the entire
Benjamin Houghton: epoch over the entire training set, or I'm sorry. Entire validation set.
Benjamin Houghton: So okay, I think that's everything.
Benjamin Houghton: now, I ran this a second ago like, and I just did 2 epochs, but it took like a little while like 2 min to do 2. And then I realized that you know
Benjamin Houghton: you know, we should add in
Benjamin Houghton: the scheduler as well. So I stopped it. Now we're gonna run it again. So I'm gonna run it for 10 epochs. And let it run. Here I'm gonna pause this recording. And then hopefully, this will be the last change
Benjamin Houghton: for this code.
Benjamin Houghton: Alright. So we're the finish running. We got some interesting results the results are worse. We remember, if you remember, we were like in the fifties or sixties, I I'm pretty sure it's because the we're we're augmenting the the images now. So it the it's gonna slow down the training.
Benjamin Houghton: it's gonna and you can see our looks like our accuracy, and our loss was still trending downwards for both the
Benjamin Houghton: test and validation data or training and testing data.
Benjamin Houghton: The testing data is kind of up and down here, but it looks like the overall trends the right direction. Not sure. But I've realized also that we were also augmenting the test data which doesn't make a whole lot of sense to do doesn't really get. So I actually updated this to not
Benjamin Houghton: so that the we weren't doing any augmentations. We're just resizing them and normalizing them. So we're going to restart. We're gonna try this one more time, and we'll see what kind of results we get this time. So I'm gonna restart the kernel. And I'm gonna run this and we'll see what happens.
Benjamin Houghton: Alright. So we finished the training. We see that
Benjamin Houghton: test. Accuracy is much better now that we're not augmenting the test images not quite
Benjamin Houghton: is high of accuracy, as maybe we would have liked. I could probably train this longer. See what happens. One thing I noticed is, I think, that
Benjamin Houghton: this is probably a topic for another day. You could look read the documentation, but
Benjamin Houghton: if I had to guess.
Benjamin Houghton: I'm just reading this warning message real fast.
Benjamin Houghton: The verbose parameter is depracted. Please use get last learning rate.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay, not too.
Benjamin Houghton: Okay. Anyways.
Benjamin Houghton: it's saying this keyword arguments depracted anyways, that's neither here nor there. I think the patience we're saying is 3 if it. I don't think I'm not sure like what the threshold is for this. But.
Benjamin Houghton: we could probably play around with some of that, those and and make this training longer, maybe get potentially get better results. But this isn't, you know, resnet
Benjamin Houghton: 18. We should be able to get about 75%. But that's with
Benjamin Houghton: full training, extensive data, augmentation and very careful hyper parameter tuning. Right? So
Benjamin Houghton: this isn't bad. For, like right out of the box, like what we did. And we're using cursor. And you know, not even what's that quarters day worth of work, if that like, you know, so not bad.
Benjamin Houghton: right out of the box like we can just use use the
Benjamin Houghton: download pre trained weights, and it kind of shows the power of of transfer learning. So and at least shows you what we're doing and and how to do it, and kind of gives you some ideas, and of course, you know you could
Benjamin Houghton: you? You could take this even further if you do all the all the things right, like hyper, parameter searches and full augmentation and all other little tricks, or maybe using even a deeper version of resnet. So anyways, that concludes the video and thanks a lot and see you guys next time.